http://www.curry.edu/privacy-policy

5th Year Master's Degrees
Program for Advancement of Learning (PAL)
Center for Career Development
Academic Student Resources
Study Abroad
Want to get ahead? Need to catch up? Take a Winter Class online!
Visit
Been Accepted?
Contact Admission Office
Come see what BECOMING at Curry is all about!
Curry Bookstore
First-Year Living Learning Communities integrate classroom and residential experiences using a holistic approach.
Contact Athletics
A Division III experience unlike any other. See what it means to be a Curry Colonel.
Contact Alumni Relations
Empower our students to achieve their ambitions. Consider a gift to Curry College today.
Give Today
Alumni
Close X
Why Curry?
Employment
Our rich liberal arts tradition, sound career focus, and empowering and supportive environment prepare our students for success.
5th Year Master's Degrees
Program for Advancement of Learning (PAL)
Visit
Been Accepted?
About Us
Why Curry?
Curry College - Home
Curry College is committed to preserving and maintaining the privacy of visitors to our websites. This Website Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for curry.edu and curryathletics.com. Curry College (hereinafter referred to as "we," "our" or "us") has compiled this policy to better serve those website visitors who are concerned with how their 'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used online.
What kind of information do we collect?
We collect two types of information: PII and aggregate information.
Generally speaking, PII is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. We have taken measures to protect such personally identifiable information from loss, misuse or alteration. Please review this policy for more information on how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.
"Aggregate information" does not identify you, and may include, for example, statistical information concerning the pages on our website that users visit more, or less, often than other pages.
What information do we gather about you, and when do we do it?
Your use of curry.edu and curryathletics.com is voluntary, and your response to any requests for information on our websites is strictly voluntary. Personal information about you is not gathered when you visit our websites unless you choose to supply that information to us. We collect information from you when you access curry.edu and curryathletics.com and when you enter information on our websites for a specific purpose, such as to subscribe to our email service, fill out a form, or participate in a live chat.
Curry College does not intend to collect any information directly from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, you may use curry.edu and curryathletics.com only with the involvement of a parent or guardian. If we learn that we have inadvertently collected information from a child under the age of 13, any and all such information will be promptly deleted from our systems.
What do we use your information for?
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website by identifying (1) which parts of our site are most heavily used, and (2) which portion of our audience comes from within the Curry College network. The College does not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable (however, some third-party partners may do so - see below). This means that user sessions will be tracked, but the users will remain anonymous.
If you choose to share it, the email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.
User information may be shared with third-party partners to the extent necessary to provide and improve web services or other communications to users. For instance, third-party partners may link the IP addresses of website users to referring media channels; this information may include the user's account information from the referring media channel. Any third parties who receive user information for this purpose are prohibited from using or sharing user information for any purpose other than providing services to users (for instance, individuals that voluntarily provide personal information to inquire about Continuing Education courses) or to the College for the purposes noted above.
We may also provide your information to third parties in circumstances where we believe that doing so is necessary or appropriate to: satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request; detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; or protect the rights, property or safety of us, our users or others.
Device Information Collected By Us
We may collect aggregate, non-personal information about the computer, mobile device or other device you use to access curry.edu and curryathletics.com, such as IP address, geolocation information, unique device identifiers, browser type, browser language or other information of this nature. We use this information in an aggregate fashion to track access to curry.edu and curryathletics.com. At no time do we disclose site usage by individual IP addresses. Web server logs are typically retained on a temporary basis and then deleted from our systems.
Cookies
Cookies are small files that are stored on your computer (unless you block them). We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. Service providers will remove your information by request.
Third-Party Cookies
Cookies may be set by an organization other than curry.edu and curryathletics.com. These "third-party cookies" may, for example, originate from websites such as YouTube, Twitter, Facebook, Google, Instagram, Live Chat or other social media services for which curry.edu and curryathletics.com has implemented "plug-ins." Since the cookie policies of these sites change over time, you should determine their policies by visiting the privacy policy pages of these sites directly.
You may disable cookies through your individual browser options. If you would like to learn more about cookies please refer to the following website: http://www.allaboutcookies.org/
EU General Data Protection Regulation
Please be aware of the Curry EU-GDPR Privacy Notice that supplements this Privacy Statement. The EU-GDPR Privacy Notice applies generally to the provision of Personal Data by individuals in the European Economic Area. The EU-GDPR Privacy Notice explains how we meet our obligations under the European Union General Data Protection Regulation with respect to such information.
Links to Third-Party Websites
We may provide hyperlinks to third-party websites as a convenience to users of curry.edu and curryathletics.com. Neither curry.edu nor curryathletics.com controls third-party websites, and we are not responsible for the contents of any linked-to, third-party websites or any hyperlink in a linked-to website. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of third-party websites.
Email Subscriptions
The @Curry Alumni e-newsletter allows you to subscribe and receive the e-newsletter via email. If you no longer wish to receive this email, follow the "unsubscribe" instructions located near the bottom of each email. If you send us email messages, you should be aware that information disclosed in email may not be secure or encrypted and thus may be available to others. We suggest that you exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personal or confidential information in email. We will use your email address to respond directly to your questions or comments.
Email Policy
We will not share, sell, rent, swap or authorize any third party to use your email address for commercial purposes without your permission.
Information Protection
Curry College engages in best efforts to comply with federal, state and local laws relating to website and data access and privacy. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the appropriate use of information we gather about you, we have taken commercially reasonable steps to protect the information. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is guaranteed to be 100% secure.
Changes to this Policy
This Privacy Policy may be amended from time to time. Any such changes will be posted on this page. The effective date of this policy was March 7, 2017. For Further Questions If you have any questions or suggestions about this Website Privacy Policy, or if you wish to contact Curry College to delete, modify or review any of your personal information that we have stored, you may contact us by sending:
an email to the following address: web at curry.edu.
U.S. mail to: Curry College Webmaster, 1071 Blue Hill Avenue, Milton, MA 02186.
Curry College Website Disclosure
We use cookies to make interactions with our websites and services easy and meaningful. By continuing to use this website, you consent to Curry College’s usage of cookies and similar technologies in accordance with the college’s Cookie Notice.
×
